翻译:neko，校对:neko，cinewamage，字幕:neko，请在下载后24小时内删除，若因私自传播造成的法律责任，字幕君概不负责。
(此字幕对应时长1:30的片源使用，请检查自己的片源获得最佳体验)
Ah, that's good.
啊，真棒啊
Do it again. Foreplay.
让我们再来一遍前♂戏
Hmm. Hmm. Hmm.
嗯♂，嗯♂~(哲学♂引擎)
I'll come all over you.
我会射你一身的♂~~~
I'm so horny.
我特么兴♂奋起来了
It's so fucking deep.
这太他喵的深了
Make me come.
我快要去♂了
I love that.
我真喜欢这样
Move your tongue around more.
把舌头动起来~
That turns me on. Yes.
这让我太性♂奋了
Oh, I'm fucking coming.
哦♂~我的枪要走火了！！！
Oh yeah. Oh yeah.
哦~液♂~
Don't stop.
别停啊魂淡
Van- Eight different penetration sounds.
Van- 八种不同的插入声音
You only make one penetrating sound.
你只搞了一种插入声。
Van- Like maybe two.
Van- 也许是两种
Haha, really? Try to branch out.
哈哈，真的吗？试着去拓展一下
Van- Fuck.
Van- 妈的
Maybe you'll discover something new about yourself.
也许你能解锁一些新的东西
Okay.
我试下
Ah!
Ouch!
好疼！
Oh, that hurts.
疼死爷了
Van- It's a fine line between sex sound and taking a dump.
Van- 性爱的声音和大便的声音之间有一条非常微妙的界限
Very fine line.
非常微妙的界限。
It's a very fine line.
这是条非常微妙的界限
Well, you know what? If you want to put some dump sounds in there, no one will ever know.
你知道吗？如果你想在那里加入一些大便的声音，没有人会知道的。
Swallow my cum.
吞下我的节操吧~
Yes.
Ah ha ha Wild.
啊哈~真狂野
You know I don't do anal.
你知道我不做肛交。
Don't touch me there.
别摸老子那儿
Do you like what you see?
你喜欢你所看到的吗？
Oh, I'm fucking cumming.
哦，老子他喵的要来♂了
Put your hands all over my soft...
把你的手放在我柔软的...
Slow down.
慢一点
Stick your finger in my ass.
将你的手指插入我的菊花
That's good.
真不错